Guide to the Stanford University, Program in African and African American Studies, Honors Theses SC4-6537
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Program in African and African American Studies, honors theses
1988-2011
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University
SC4-6537
.5 Linear Feet (9 volumes in 2 boxes)
Honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Program in African and African American Studies.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Program in African and African American Studies.
Access to Collection
The collection is open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Acquisition Information
Theses were transferred to the Stanford University Archives from the Hume Writing Center in 2011.
Stanford University
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-152
  - Holloran, Peter H., Education for social change: the citizenship education program of the Highlander Folk School and the SCLC., 1988 (Box 1)
  - Maloney, Christopher, Strike to change: an economic history of labor and control in apartheid South Africa, 1922-1994., 2002 (Box 1)
  - Sampson, Kaila, Mirror, mirror, on the wall -- who is fairest of them all? Representations of blackness in Disneyland., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Irvin, Steven, Roy DeCarava: portrait of an artist., 1989 (Box 1)
  - Lane, Stephanie, Heritage tourism and challenges to African American identity: a psychological study of African American tourists to Ghana., 2003 (Box 1)
  - Thomas, Holly A., And judges for all? Judge Ronnie White, the Fourth Circuit Court of Appeals, and the role of race in federal judicial selection., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Cruz, Ariane, Kings: resistance and fame in graffiti and the art of Jean-Michel Basquiat., 2000 (Box 1)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2018-060
  - Quinlan, Krystal Erin, "The ethnogenesis of afrodescendientes in Chile: Lumbanga's role in the contemporary ethnic identity formation of Afro-Chileans", 2006 Aug 2 (Box 1)
  - White, Darius T., "Too young to "know," old enough to tell; analysis of youth mentoring from the perspective of youth of color", 2011 May 25 (Box 1)